Good morning. Would you like to know what
results came yesterday and how were those results? So
first of all, we are going to talk about IndusInd
Bank's lazy inline set of numbers
and the acid quality has also remained
stable. Talking about this, here
also a lazy inline set of numbers has come
and there is some stability in the margins as well.
However, a slight decline of 60 basis points has
definitely been seen sequentially. We have
seen weak set of numbers like this for Lambert. And here the portion number,
although a 12% speaker gross has been seen,
if we talk about this specialty, then
very strong numbers have come and this test match has been
beaten. There is a fall of 87% in EVDA. If we
talk about automatic, then a
slightly weak set of numbers have come because the
portions have beaten the analysts,
which are actually not met and
its impact is because there has been a
slight impact on the European business of
JSW.  A very mixed set of
numbers have come in regarding this. Finally, I will talk about the
operational update. There, we
saw excellent results for Add Any Transmission.
Both the transmission network and power transmission capacity increased by 5 to 15% each on
your own basis. The
results were as follows.